

# Ralph Martyn Esteva

Front End Developer | UI/UX Designer



+63-945-317-8169



rapesteva.com



rapsamaniego27@gmail.com



2 Ford St. Phase 3c, Filinvest East Homes, Antipolo City



I'm a persuasive, confident individual pursuing a career in Web Development. I specialize in working on Front End and UI/UX Design. I'm looking forward to creating for the world with you.



- •HTMI
- •CSS/SASS
- Javascrip
- NPM / Yarn
- DLID
- •Wordnress
- lekyl

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adohe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Wireframing
- Prototypino
- JAMstack Dev

### • Education

Jose Rizal University
 BSBA Major in Computer Science
 (2011 - 2016)



- Soleil Olandez
   Project Manager
   olandezsoleil@gmail.com
- Lian Ines
  Inbound Marketing Specialist

## Work Experience

### Web Development Associate

Mad About Solutions

Aug 2019 - Feb 2022

Handled WordPress based websites, managing them through FTP clients. Also developed sites provided by Graphic Designers from a PSD file. Responsible also for providing User Manuals for usage of the clients' site.

### Web Development Specialist I

Mar 2017 - Aug 2019

StraightArrow Corporation

Responsible for developing HTML email templates and landing pages for, managing marketing campaigns and setting up blast schedule with use of the Marketing Cloud platform.

#### Web Designer

Asiatravel.com

Jun 2016 - Feb 2017

This position involves designing marketing materials, creating and coding microsites, debugging and maintaining asiatravel.com web content.



### Modern Javascript From The Beginning

**Brad Traversy** 

Aug 2020

## UI/UX using Adobe Experience Design

Creative Nation Academy

Aug 2019

## **Professional Employment Program**

Ayala Education Incorporated

Apr 2016